Speaker: Part 2
Mrs. Myers turned over the first card.
“The seven of diamonds. That means money. You’re going to be rich!
And the jack of hearts!
That’s a good card. It means you’re going to meet a young man.”
“Ah,” said Mrs. McCleary. “And what next?”
“The ten of spades,” said Mrs. Myers, as she turned over the third card.
“That means you’re going to travel.
But then,” she exclaimed,
“we have the king of clubs! Clubs always mean problems.
Somebody’s going to try to stop you. An old man…”
“Probably my father!” Mrs. McCleary exclaimed.
“But let’s look at the last card,” said Mrs. Myers.
“Ah! The queen of hearts!
You’re going to fall in love with the young man.
Dear Miss Jones, in one year’s time, you’re going to marry a very rich young man,
a businessman – he travels a lot.
An old man is going to try to stop your marriage, but he’s not going to succeed.
You’re going to move far away from here, probably abroad.
That will be one pound, please.”
“Thank you so much,” said Mrs. McCleary.
She took a pound from her purse and gave it to Mrs. Myers.
“Thank you,” said Mrs. Myers.
“Goodbye, my dear Miss Jones…
Next, please!”
When Mrs. McCleary got home, she told her husband everything.
“I don’t like it,” Inspector McCleary said.
“What should we do about her? I know! I’ll report her.”
And that’s what Inspector McCleary did.